Spokane, WA

j03grassl@gmail.com 509-808-4235

Introduction

I believe that the best defense is a good offense, so I'd like to work in the exciting world of penetration testing, red teaming, and application security. I've been studying computer security for several years and have competed in many security capture-the-flag challenges and competitions. You can find some examples of my skills and previous projects on my Github repos, my HackTheBox account, and my personal website.

Github: https://github.com/delta-plus

HackTheBox: https://app.hackthebox.eu/profile/36433

Website: https://delta-plus.github.io

Education

• Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, Eastern Washington University – 2022

• Minor in Cybersecurity, Eastern Washington University – 2022

• Associate's Degree in Network Design, Spokane Community College – 2019

Experience

- Security Engineer at TorchLight 2022
- Open-source web forum development for CiviWiki 2018
- Freelance web scraper and bot development 2017 to 2018
- Freelance Android app development in React Native 2017 to 2018
- Intern at Tierpoint, a data center and computer security services provider in Liberty Lake, WA 2015
- Occasional laptop repair and virus removal 2015 to Present

Skills

Linux and Windows Administration:

Scripting, system and network configuration, security hardening, forensics.

• Programming:

C, C#, C++, Java, Python, HTML/CSS/JS, React, React Native, bash, batch, PowerShell, Node.js, and assembly.

Networking:

Deep knowledge of ports, protocols, OSI layers, infrastructure, network design, virtualization, and cloud computing.

· Cybersecurity:

Web security, reverse engineering, Windows and Linux hacking, network security, and Android security.

Some of my favorite tools are radare2, impacket, Bloodhound, Sliver, ffuf, ripgrep, crackmapexec, nmap, hashcat, sleuthkit, sqlmap, dnSpy, as well as tmux, vim, and custom scripts.

Awards

- 2nd Place Spokane Mayor's Cup Cybersecurity Competition 2022
- 2nd Place Spokane Mayor's Cup Cybersecurity Competition 2019
- 3rd Place in the nation for Network Design, Future Business Leaders of America 2016
- 6th Place in the nation for Cybersecurity, Future Business Leaders of America 2015

Certifications

- CompTIA Security+ Currently studying, should complete by August 2022
- Cisco CCNA 10/2019
- Cisco CCNA Routing & Switching 10/2019
- CompTIA Linux+ 12/2018
- Microsoft Technology Associate: Security Fundamentals 5/2015
- Microsoft Technology Associate: Networking Fundamentals 5/2015